

P V Venugopal

p.v.venugopallakshmi@gmail.com Mobile:9087039037 24(New No:11) Ellaiamman kovil street, West Mambalam, chennai-33

Passionate electrical engineer with hand on experience in wide range of technologies expertise in covering ideas into porotypes developing products with ease of installation and services.

EXPERIENCE

India Intellisys technology private ltd, Chennai (System Admin-Contract) - March 2021 - Present

- Maintaining all system and network and windows server 2012,
- ➤ If any issue happens in laptop or desktop resolve it, making report of overall asset purchasing and services cost and pep data,
- Chip level servicing the laptop and desktop,
- Cisco router and switches installation, configuration, arranging new assets to user configure everything like drivers and server access

COGNIZANT, Sholinganallur- asset Management - November 2020 - Feb 2021

- Contract based employee, Daily bms data maintain and ticket raising,
- Asset issue rectify and hardware issue resolve, maintain stocks in asset store data both online and offline, receiving new stocks from courier and updating bms in online,
- Laptop os installation and solve bug & error then chip-level fault identifies,
- ➢ Blue screen error solves and change ram DDR3,4 in laptop

ASAHI INDIA GLASS PVT LTD, Sriperumbudur — PPC - May - 2019 - March 2020

- Production planning control (ppc), Subassembly planning and production data record maintain,
- Shift Wise plan schedule creator and supervising,
- Monthly production cost (PEP data) summary calculation, Rotational shift job

IIFL BUILDING, Chennai — technician - July 2018 — April 2019.

➤ High voltage 11kv-220v substation electrical maintenance work, floor ups maintenance for IT company's up to 9 floors, contract-based employee under based Surya facilities service

Education

BHARATH UNIVERSITY, Chennai — B.tech(EEE) JULY 2014 – MAY 2018.

Completed graduated in electrical and electronics engineering with over all CGPA-8.

OXFORD MATRIC HR SEC.SCHOOL, Chennai -JUNE 2013- MARCH 2014

Completed higher secondary school with Over all percentage is 70%

SMR MATRIC HR SEC.SCHOOL, Chennai -JUNE 2012- MAR 2013

Completed high school with Over all percentage is 65%

SKILLS

- > Hardware Skills
- Computer Assemble, Laptop Service, Networking Hardware & Security software skills
- ➤ Windows Os, C,C++ , Quick book & Multimedia Skills
- Photoshop, Ms Office

AWARDS/CERTIFICATES

- Certificate in NETWORKING CONCEPTS WITH SECURITY at V3tech solutions, Ashok Nagar
- In Alison website i Completed Courses of multiple domains hosting on one virtual server
- In Alison website I completed courses of windows server administrator
- In Alison website I completed courses of Microsoft teams
- Implant training for 7 days in POWER TRANSSMISION AND DISTRIBUTION at 230/110 KV KADAPERI SUB STATION.
- Organizer in the University Technical Festival 'SPIKE' 2017
- Participated in XPONDERS '15 to present a paper on LI-FI Technology in St. Peter's University on 2015
- Attended 'NATIONAL LEVEL TECHNICAL SYMPOSIUM' in St. Peter's University on 2015
- Participated in 'ROBO SUMO WAR' in EXPRO'17 held on March'17 in Madras Institute of Technology

LANGUAGES spoken

- > TAMIL,
- ➤ ENGLISH

Father Name: Venkatarangan PV

DOB: 12.01.1997

Religion: Hindu

Marital Status: Married

Place: Yours Truly, Chennai

Date: (P.V.

Venugopal)